oneted.de 2019-05-31

# Privacy Policy – oneted

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

#### What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

We do not collect information from visitors of our site. or other details to help you with your experience.

#### How do we protect information?

We only provide articles and information. We never ask for credit card numbers. We use regular Malware Scanning.

We do not use an SSL certificate as we only provide articles and information. We never ask for personal or private information like names, email addresses, or credit card numbers.

On every occasion where we have to transmit sensitive information we will be using modern encryption methods to ensure your data is safe.

#### Do we use 'cookies'?

We do not use cookies for tracking purposes. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. That make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.

However, you will still be able to use our services with cookies turned off.

#### Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.

#### Third-party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### Google

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en

Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google's own privacy policies. 

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the United States of America to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

While our office is in Germany and therefore we are under german law, we still try to hit these goals for our american customers. 

##### According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:

Users can visit our site anonymously.  
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.  
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' or 'Datenschutz' (german) and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes: 

  * On our Privacy Policy Page

You can change your personal information 
  * by emailing us
  * by logging in to your account (if existing)

##### Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?

It's also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking 

#### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

While our office is in Germany and therefore we are under german law, we still do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

#### Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information. While our office is in Germany and therefore we are under german law, we still try to hit these goals for our american customers. 

##### In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:

  * We will notify you via email within 1 business day
  * We will notify the users via in-site notification within 1 business day

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors. 

#### CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations. 

##### We do not collect your email address!

##### However to be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:

  * Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
  * Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

##### If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at

  * Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.

and we will promptly remove you from **ALL** correspondence. 

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below. Kaan Özet Edelstr. 2 Albershausen, BW 73095 Germany support@oneted.de Last Edited on 2016-07-11
